

Nicholas Owen

C

(+62) 812 8062 6658



owen.djohan@gmail.com



Nicholas Owen | LinkedIn



<u>Sertifikat</u>

SUMMARY

Im a graduate of Bina Nusantara University, majoring in Computer Science where I learned various things which I will list in my skills below. I'm used to environments that involve teamwork and am experienced enough in workplace culture. I'm a fast learner and I'm willing to learn any new skills for the benefit of my workplace. Currently working as Developer in PT. Bank Artha Graha Internasional Tbk.

SKILLS

-Office

-Java

-PHP

-C

-HTML

-C#

-CSS

-T24 Temenos

-JS

-Laravel

-MySQL

-PostGre SQL

EDUCATION

SMA

PKBM 19 2016-2018

S₁/S.Kom

Binus University 2018-2022

EXPERIENCE

Intern

Esri Indonesia/Jakarta/2020-2022

Intern/Junior Developer for a year at Esri Indonesia. Participated at Geospatial Artificial Intelligence International Short Course & Hackathon Webmap Competition.

- Development of Geo Application
- Development of Webmap
- Hackathon participation

IT/Technical Support

PT Duta Nitsuko Abadi/Jakarta/2022

Worked full-time as developer in PT Duta Nitsuko Abadi. Work activity includes PBX server setup and development of company web profile.

- PBX setup and programming
- PBX Maintenance
- Web Development

Relationship Manager

PT. Bank OCBC NISP Tbk./Jakarta/2023

Worked full time as Retail Funding Relationship Manager in Bank OCBC NISP. The job involves wealth management and marketing.

- Certified Insurance Seller with AAJI
- Wealth Management

Developer

PT.Indo Artha Teknologi/Jakarta/2023-Now

Worked full-time at PT.Indo Artha Teknologi, job includes development of applications and programs for Banking or Non Banking purposes.

- Backend developer of Human Capital Apps
- T-24 Development
- AGP Market Application

Staff Developer

PT.Bank Artha graha Internasional Tbk./Jakarta/2024-Now

Worked full-time currently at PT.Bank Artha Graha Internasional Tbk. Currently developing backend applications for Artha Graha with T24 Temenos system.

- T-24 Development
- Core Banking System Migration
- Data Mapping and Queries